

FLORENT TANDJUNE TAMOYEM

Software developer

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Contact

Meisenweg 10, App 150 67663 Kaiserslautern, Germany tandjunetamoyem@gmail.com +49 1577 8272863 Nationality Cameroonian

Date and place of birth

25/10/1995 Mbouda

PROFILE

II am an experienced frontend and backend developer who has gained knowledge in various areas of software development.

Through projects I have accumulated good experience with languages such as Javascript (Typescript, Vue.js, react, Angular), php (Laravel), Python, Java (spring boot).

As far as mobile app development (Android/iOS) is concerned, I have experience with Android Studio, Swift, Flutter, React Native and everything related to PWA (Progressive Web App).

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Developer, SPIE RODIAS GmbH, Weinheim

FEBRUARY 2023 - JULY 2024

My work mainly consists of developing new solutions to customer problems, implementing new customer requirements in ongoing projects, testing the user interface of applications and fixing bugs.

Technologies used: Kotlin, Java, Typscript, JEST, SQL, Docker, JSON, Ubuntu

Developer, SalonDigital GbR, Grünstadt

FEBRUARY 2022 - JULY 2022

My task was to design and develop the website for the management of a beauty shop.

Technologies used: HTML, CSS, Javascript(Vue.js, Vuetify).

EDUCATION

Master, RPTU Kaiserslautern

October 2022 - CURRENTLY

After successfully completing my Bachelor's degree, I decided to do my Master's degree at the RPTU in Kaiserslautern, specialising in Software Engineering and Embedded Systems and Robotics.

Bachelor, RPTU Kaiserslautern

APRIL 2018 - July 2023

After the language course, I started studying computer science at RPTU Kaiserslautern, where I completed my Bachelor's degree.

DSH Exam, TU Darmstadt

FEBRUARY 2018 - MARCH 2018

I spent a week preparing for the DSH exam offered by the TU Darmstadt. At the end of that week, I took the exam.

German course, Goethe Institut, Yaoundé

DECEMBER 2015 - JULY 2017

I learnt German at the Goethe-Institut in Cameroon for about a year and a half. I received a c1 certificate there.

Study, Universität von Yaoundé 1, Ngoa- kélé

SEPTEMBER 2014 - DECEMBER 2015

After my high school graduation, I studied biochemistry for about three semesters.

High school, Lycée de Nkozoa, Soa

SEPTEMBER 2011 - JUNE 2014

I spent my last three years of high school at this school and obtained my high school degree there.

LINKS

Portfolio GitHub LinkedIn

FÄHIGKEITEN

Kotlin	F#
Javascript	Linux
Python	Node.js
Java	HTML/CSS
SQL	Docker
Vue.js	Git
React	Multitasking ability
PHP	Fast learner
TypeScript	Team spirit
	Communication skills
LANGUAGES	German
French	
English	
g	

PERSONAL PROJECT

okike TV

OCTOBER 2021

okikeTV is an online TV channel that offers a wide range of TV shows, films, cartoons, documentaries and much more on thousands of Internet-connected devices.

Technologies used: VueJS, Artefact, Strapi (backend), NodeJS (streaming and real-time scheduling)

VOLUNTEERING

NASA Space Apps Challenge, Kaiserslautern

MARCH 2021 - OCTOBER 2021

I was part of the organisation team of the Nasa Space Apps 2021 Challenge at my university (RPTU Kaiserslautern) and was responsible for communication.

JustCodeKL, Kaiserslautern

NOVEMBER 2019 - CURRENTLY

JustCodeKL is a student group at RPTU Kaiserslautern that helps students gain work experience during their studies. It supports students in their job search in IT companies.

HOBBYS

In my free time, I like listening to music and watching documentaries. And when the weather is nice, I like to go for walks, play football or go jogging.